<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jay Khabra - Full Stack Developer</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Jay Khabra - Full Stack Developer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How I utilize Github actions to automate my personal site</title><link>/blog/utilize-github-actions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/utilize-github-actions/</guid><description>I have created this site in Hugo. The purpose of this site to showcase my work, skills and share my thoughts. Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators. I chose hugo because there is big range of free Hugo themes available. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to invest too much in creating the theme myself. I chose osprey theme written by tomanistor, which I found very pleasing.
Using hugo is easy enough, but I wanted a completely effort-less development environment like we have in SoS app.</description></item><item><title>I'm Jay Khabra</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 12:36:41 -0700</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>A web developer in Mohail, Punjab. let languages = [&amp;#39;javascript&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;python&amp;#39;], frameworks = [&amp;#39;reactjs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;nextjs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;hapijs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;flask&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;graphql&amp;#39;], tools = [&amp;#39;nodejs&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;postgres&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;mongo&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;hasura&amp;#39;], skillset = languages.concat(frameworks, tools) View my code on GitHub, connect with me on LinkedIn, follow me on Twitter, and check out my work below.</description></item><item><title>THE SOS APP</title><link>/portfolio/the-sos-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 15:58:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/the-sos-app/</guid><description>An open source project we are building for ourselves. Goal of the project is:
To establish transparent communication between software development team To keep the entire team motivated and focused on what we want to achieve To ensure smooth progress so no-one is blocked by someone else on the team (very common in software dev teams) To ensure highest quality of work To gradually build a knowledge base, so team don&amp;rsquo;t repeat their mistakes, and don&amp;rsquo;t waste time re-researching same problems The application is 100% conceptualized, designed and developed by our in-house team.</description></item><item><title>Pharmacy App</title><link>/gallery/pharmacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:57:17 -0800</pubDate><guid>/gallery/pharmacy/</guid><description>Summary Pharmacy App is a mobile app and built for android and ios. In this app users can book pharmacies then app finds the nearby delivery agents (around rage in 3 km). When agents accept the booking then the app holds the delivery amount. This app uses the credit score (Aduro money) as well.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Hapi.js Developing WebSocket based realtime APIs Developing an admin panel using React and Redux Collaborating with Android and IOS teams to provide support and guidance for integrating APIs Technologies Node.</description></item><item><title/><link>/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Taxi App</title><link>/gallery/taxiapp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/taxiapp/</guid><description>Summary &amp;ldquo;Taxi App&amp;rdquo; was a client project i did during my full time employment. it was done on a very tight deadline under minimum supervision. It is like a clone of uber/ola.
Responsibilities i was responsible for
developing rest apis using hapi.js developing websocket based realtime apis developing an admin panel using react and redux collaborating with android and ios teams to provide support and guidance for integrating apis Technologies node.</description></item><item><title>Resto-Find</title><link>/gallery/restaurantfinder/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 21:57:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/restaurantfinder/</guid><description>Summary Resto Find is an app which users can find and book restaurants. It is Zomato clone. In this app users can add their restaurant then admin can approve/reject it. Users can login with Google, faceBook or create app account. This app provides deals and offers to users as well.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Hapi.js Developing a web interface and admin panel using React and Redux Handled payment with stripe and paypal Technologies Node.</description></item><item><title>WallFeed (chrome extensions)</title><link>/gallery/wallfeed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:57:17 -1200</pubDate><guid>/gallery/wallfeed/</guid><description>Summary WallFeed is a chrome extension. In this extension users can see posts and users can suggest the post url to admin. Admin can approve/reject users suggestions and if admin approves the suggestion then post displays on the home page. In Lettertab users can search posts, sort posts with views, sort with share and sort with tags.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Hapi.js Developing an admin panel using React and Redux Developing an extensions (ui) in react Developing responsive designs Handle auth flow with google, facebook, linkedin and twitter Technologies Node.</description></item><item><title>SoS App</title><link>/gallery/sosapp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:52:57 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/sosapp/</guid><description>Summary SoS is an insolent app meant for Software Development teams to be more effective in creating good quality software.
It does so by bringing transparency in your team and by aiming to save you from meetings.
Being an insolent software, you can start using it without waiting on anyone to adopt it organization wide. Although to get most out of SoS, it is better if you join along your team.</description></item><item><title>Brato</title><link>/gallery/brato/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:52:57 -1400</pubDate><guid>/gallery/brato/</guid><description>Summary Brato App offers a fun and mindful way to get all that you desire. It’s a way for you to get value out of your stuff and your talents or service. There’s NO money evolved in this process. It is just a brato (brater) way. Users can make a deal, and will likely meet a few awesome people along the way!
Responsibilities i was responsible for
developing rest apis using Python Flask developing an admin panel using react and redux developing web app using react with responsive design Technologies Python Flask for Backend Postgres for persistence Redis for supporting sessions and websockets React for Frontend with Redux</description></item></channel></rss>