<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Galleries on Jay Khabra - Full Stack Developer</title><link>/gallery/</link><description>Recent content in Galleries on Jay Khabra - Full Stack Developer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 22:25:16 -1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/gallery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AtCash Time</title><link>/gallery/time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 22:25:16 -1100</pubDate><guid>/gallery/time/</guid><description>Summary Atcash Time provides a service to verify users Identity. Validate passports, driver&amp;rsquo;s licenses, social. security numbers and more. TIME FOR IDENTITY.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Express.js Developing WebSocket based realtime APIs Developing WebSocket and webRTC for video call Developing ui using React and Redux Collaborating with Android and IOS teams to provide support and guidance for integrating APIs Technologies Node.js/Express.js Socket.io for websockets WebRTC Mongodb for persistence Redis for supporting sessions and websockets React.</description></item><item><title>Aduro Pharmacy App</title><link>/gallery/pharmacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:57:17 -0800</pubDate><guid>/gallery/pharmacy/</guid><description>Summary Pharmacy App is a mobile app and built for android and ios. In this app users can book pharmacies then app finds the nearby delivery agents (around rage in 3 km). When agents accept the booking then the app holds the delivery amount. This app uses the credit score (Aduro money) as well.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Hapi.js Developing WebSocket based realtime APIs Developing an admin panel using React and Redux Collaborating with Android and IOS teams to provide support and guidance for integrating APIs Technologies Node.</description></item><item><title>Ron Taxi</title><link>/gallery/rontaxi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:25:02 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/rontaxi/</guid><description>Summary &amp;ldquo;Ron taxi&amp;rdquo; was a client project i did during my full time employment at yapapp. it was done on a very tight deadline under minimum supervision. It is like a clone of uber/ola.
Responsibilities i was responsible for
developing rest apis using hapi.js developing websocket based realtime apis developing an admin panel using react and redux collaborating with android and ios teams to provide support and guidance for integrating apis Technologies node.</description></item><item><title>Early Table</title><link>/gallery/earlytable/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 21:57:17 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/earlytable/</guid><description>Summary Early-Table is an app which users can find and book restaurants. In this app users can add their restaurant then admin can approve/reject it. Users can login with Google, faceBook or create Early-table account. This app provides deals and offers to users as well.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Hapi.js Developing a web interface and admin panel using React and Redux Handled payment with stripe and paypal Technologies Node.</description></item><item><title>Lettertab (chrome extensions)</title><link>/gallery/letterlab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:57:17 -1200</pubDate><guid>/gallery/letterlab/</guid><description>Summary Lettertab is a chrome extension. In this extension users can see posts and users can suggest the post url to admin. Admin can approve/reject users suggestions and if admin approves the suggestion then post displays on the home page. In Lettertab users can search posts, sort posts with views, sort with share and sort with tags.
Responsibilities I was responsible for
Developing REST APIs using Hapi.js Developing an admin panel using React and Redux Developing an extensions (ui) in react Developing responsive designs Handle auth flow with google, facebook, linkedin and twitter Technologies Node.</description></item><item><title>SoS App</title><link>/gallery/sosapp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:52:57 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/sosapp/</guid><description>Summary SoS is an insolent app meant for Software Development teams to be more effective in creating good quality software.
It does so by bringing transparency in your team and by aiming to save you from meetings.
Being an insolent software, you can start using it without waiting on anyone to adopt it organization wide. Although to get most out of SoS, it is better if you join along your team.</description></item><item><title>Brato</title><link>/gallery/brato/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:52:57 -1400</pubDate><guid>/gallery/brato/</guid><description>Summary Brato App offers a fun and mindful way to get all that you desire. It’s a way for you to get value out of your stuff and your talents or service. There’s NO money evolved in this process. It is just a brato (brater) way. Users can make a deal, and will likely meet a few awesome people along the way!
Responsibilities i was responsible for
developing rest apis using Python Flask developing an admin panel using react and redux developing web app using react with responsive design Technologies Python Flask for Backend Postgres for persistence Redis for supporting sessions and websockets React for Frontend with Redux</description></item></channel></rss>